[{"answer": "It's fine. I can just get you at your office", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Ok, bye, bye", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Ok", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Bye", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I thought they opened at seven.  If I left my car would it be ok", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Do you know them", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Are you going to the party tonight", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What are you doing", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You can't be late", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm serious", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ok", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'll see you there", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Hi my friend", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Business is very food, thanks. ELIZABETH What's very food", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " It's ok, take your time", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " No one will know your name", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Hi. This is my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "This is that place", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "So what are you doing tonight, my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah. And looking at myself in the mirror. Do you wanna know what I look like", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What do you mean it doesn't matter", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'm fine. Who is this", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I can't really. Yeah, no. I mean. I can't afford it", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I know but I....how much is it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yes I do", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No. No. We got disconnect", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't have a girlfriend", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I know I did. But I don't", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You lied to me", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Why did you tell me you did, then", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Come on, I thought we had fun, rich boy", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It was cool last night", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I feel really on the spot now", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I don't do that. I don't", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I don't do that. I don't", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'm not being scared, you're just going to rag me if I do this", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You don't do anything, why are you being scared", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm not gonna rag you. Why would I do this just to rag you", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I'm not being scared, you're just going to rag me if I do this", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "-- well, if you're gonna go", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I was, yeah, I was thinking about going there for business", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "-- I'm probably not gonna go though", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "If we drive there it's a problem", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Which one", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Yeah, no, I see", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "You see", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You see if you spent", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "....No...", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "No I didn't say that", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "There's a better place for us to eat", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Yes I'm fine. Everything is ok. It's fine. Everything is fine", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Ok", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I don't, no matter what my sisters say, ok", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "I don't freak out", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "What do you have in the house", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You have an ATM", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Where you goin", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Wow, you're goin' to that place, that's great", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "......she forgot her purse at my work and I wanted to get it back to her", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I....please don't do this", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well let's do something do you want to do something, can you meet me", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "No. What do you mean? my friend just wanted to know. When was the last time you had a boyfriend", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "...people are just crazy in this world, I think...", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "The first man came on the driver side...", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "You better watch your mouth, cunt, you're gonna get hurt", "docId": "Punch-Drunk-Love.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "I'll say whatever I want", "qsentId": 76}]